Sophia Tsivoula



Contact

sophia.sts.21@gmail.com p18tsiv@ionio.gr sophia-tsivoula sophia-ts

Education

BSc in Computer Science Ionian University 2018 - 2022

Languages

Greek (Native)
English (Professional)
French (Elementary)

Skills HTML CSS Python MySQL

Career Profile

I am a passionate Junior Web Developer and Researcher interested in modern web technologies and medical applications. Personally enjoy volunteering and work with large groups of people. I ram able to communicate with both technical and not technical colleagues and I am able to make critical decisions for the benefit of many. I can be described as hard working, reliable and resourceful in demanding projects.

Experience

Web Develoment

Lingua Technis 2019 - 2020

Developed a personalized multilingual CV for translation services using WordPress. The personalized CV contained, besides general information about the client, a contact page, a list of the services the client could offer and the option to send via email document for translation on both German and English.

Research

Ionian University

2019 - Present

Presented a scientific paper called "An application for exploring visual perception. A pilot neuroeducational study." And presented it in GeNeDis 2020 (Worldwide congress). The application's goal was the neuroeducation of the human brain for individual with cognitive difficulties. The users had to observe an image for a few seconds and recreate it from memory on an empty canvas using their mobile device.

Volunteering

TEDx Ionian University

IT team

2019 - Present

Developed a presentation website and an e-shop for selling tickets for a virtual event. The website was created on WordPress using the Divi Visual Builder.

Ionian IEEE Student Branch

Activity Planning Manager

2020 - Present

Organized the activity planning team on the IEEE Ionian Student Branch and planned two successful webinars.